黑 鏡
圣朱尼佩洛
捉鬼小精靈
塔克酒吧
以上是貝琳達·卡萊爾
Belinda Carlisle there
為您帶來1987年目前最熱的一首歌
with one of the biggest hits of 1987 so far.
這首歌不能不愛  稍后...
Gotta love that track! Coming up next in just a moment...
你夠了好嗎  我只想找點樂子
Could you please stop it? I just wanna have some fun, okay?
凱莉  得了
Kelly, come on.
-凱莉  -我還走著呢  韋斯
- Kelly. - I'm still walking, Wes.
我們只有幾小時  我們好好利用吧
We've only got a couple of hours so let's, uh... let's use it.
我在好好利用
I am using it.
字幕組
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
最新最快海外影視字幕下載
翻譯：小酸奶  草草  showeryhe  瀟然
校對：草草
時間軸：黑查
后期：吉吉  總監：草草
你挺厲害
You're good at this.
有不同的結局
It's, uh... got different endings.
要看是一個玩家還是兩個
Depending on if you're in one or two player.
-這是第一款有這種設置的游戲  -該死
- It was kinda the first game to do that. - Damn it!
你想玩《全速前進》嗎
Do you wanna play Top Speed?
不
Oh, no.
謝謝
Thank you.
我只想熟悉下這里
I just wanna get my bearings a bit.
好吧
Okay.
回見
See you around?
配合我
Go along with whatever I say.
-什么  -配合我接話
- Sorry? - Whatever I say, go along with it.
好吧  韋斯  你這樣就是纏人了
Okay, Wes, you're just pestering now.
-要我給你亮紅燈嗎  -2小時35分
- Do I have to red light you? - Two hours 35.
-沒剩多少時間了  -韋斯
- There's not much time left. - Wes.
聽著
Look...
上周我們發生了最美妙的...
Last week, we had the most amazing--
那是上周了
Last week was last week.
我得跟我朋友聊會兒天
I need to talk with my friend here, okay?
我好久沒見她了
Haven't seen her in a while.
韋斯  她病了
Wes, she's sick.
只剩"六個月"那種病
Like "six months to live" sick.
其實是五個月
Five, actually.
我得跟她敘舊  就我倆
I need to catch up with her. Private time.
好吧
Okay.
-很遺憾  -沒事
- Hey, I'm sorry. - That's okay.
回見
See you around?
好啊
Sure.
抱歉我"殺"了你
Sorry for killing you.
那個什么"只剩六個月"
The whole "six months to live" thing?
抱歉  是五個月
Sorry. Five.
你說五個月真挺像回事
Five was a nice touch.
-凱莉  -約克夏
- Kelly. - Yorkie.
-尤克  -約克夏
-Yurgie? - Yorkie.
跟狗種一樣嗎
Like the dog breed?
是啊
Yeah.
他人不壞  我有點過意不去
He's not a bad guy. I feel kinda bad.
-在"泥潭"認識他的...  -那是什么
- Met him at the Quagmire so... - What's the Quagmire?
你如果還不知道"泥潭"
If you don't already know what the Quagmire is,
那你估計也不會想知道的
you probably don't wanna know.
是嗎
No?
想再來一杯嗎
You want another one?
-不了  -要的  來吧
- Oh, no, I-- - Yeah, you do. Come on.
還要我拽你的狗鏈嗎
Do I have to tug your leash?
-金發帥哥  -喊我
- Hey, Blondie. - I'm Blondie?
你就是  威士忌可樂  兩杯
You are. Jack and Coke times two.
-不  我那杯就可樂  -兩杯
- Oh, no. Mine was just a Coke. - Times two.
-你干什么  -我在端詳你
- What are you doing? - I'm... regarding you.
我覺得你在分析我
I feel like I'm being analysed.
為什么戴眼鏡
Why the glasses?
我挺喜歡  很合適你  但你需要戴嗎
I like them. They totally work on you. But do you need them?
-嗯  是平光鏡  -我就知道
- Yeah, the lenses don't do anything. - Knew it!
我以前上學時戴
I used to wear them in school.
所以現在算是...讓我寬心吧
So I guess now they're just kind of a... comfort thing.
我還以為是你的時尚聲明呢
I figured they were kind of a fashion statement.
-是嗎  -但從你的衣著看又不像
- Really? - But then the rest of your outfit is not.
別誤會  挺新鮮的  看看周圍啊
Don't take that wrong. It's refreshing. I mean, look around.
大家都刻意打扮成他們以為自己該打扮成的樣子
People try so hard to look how they think they should look.
可能是在哪部電影里看到的
They probably saw it in some movie.
但我喜歡這個
But I like these.
你是真實的你
You're authentically you.
謝謝
Thanks.
干杯
Cheers.
你試過嗎
You never tasted it before?
不是
No, I...
我就是好久沒喝過了  挺好的
I just haven't had it in a while. It's good.
你住這兒嗎
Do you live here?
-不...  -游客嗎
- No. Oh, uh-- - Tourist?
就算是游客吧  你是新來的
We'll go with tourist. So you're new here?
-第一晚  -是嗎  好吧
- First night. - First night? Wow, okay!
天吶
Oh, my God!
我們必須跳舞
We have to dance to this.
我們跳嗎
With each other?
算了  我不適應舞池
Oh, no. Dance floors aren't my thing.
別限制自己嘛
Oh, let's not limit ourselves.
-我真不行  -你可以的  來吧
- No, I can't. - Yes, you can, come on.
-不  我會冒傻氣的  -跟著我來就好
- No, I'll look dumb-- - Just follow my lead!
學我的樣子
Copy me.
你行的
You got it.
-你為什么逃跑  -對不起
- Why did you run away? - Oh, sorry.
我說了  我不太會跳舞
I... I said I'm not much of a dancer.
可不是
No shit.
你剛剛就像冰湖上被嚇壞的馬
Like a frightened horse on a frozen lake back there.
我開玩笑的  半開玩笑吧
I'm kidding. Half kidding.
對不起我逼你跳了
Sorry I pushed you into it.
每周一個周六夜  一晃而過  我會不耐煩
Saturday nights once a week. It's like no time. I get impatient.
不  不是那個
No, no, it's not that. It's...
-大家都在看我  -看你
- Everyone was looking. - Looking?
是啊  兩個姑娘跳舞
Yeah. You know, two girls dancing.
首先  人們不像過去那么刻板了
Okay, one, folks are way less uptight than they used to be.
其次  這是派對之城  沒人會說什么的
And two, this is a party town. No one's judging.
承認吧
Face it.
即使他們看了  也因為非凡的我
If they were staring, it's because I am bodacious.
-你好傻  -謝謝
- You're stupid. - Thank you!
-我從沒進過舞池  -從沒嗎
- I've never been on a dance floor. - Never?
就是你活這么大從沒嗎
As in the whole time you've been alive never?
從沒
Never.
信仰返璞歸真生活的教派
你是阿米什人嗎
What are you, like, Amish?
你的生活也太閉塞了吧
That's one sheltered existence you got there.
是啊
Yeah, well.
我家人覺得我什么都做不了
As far as my family's concerned, I can't do anything.
我干的壞事別人連一半都不知道
Well, no one knows about even half the shit I get up to.
不過就你爸媽而言
With your folks, though,
他們也是出自關心吧
it's from a place of love, though, right?
-他們是擔心你  -他們不是擔心
- They worry. - They don't worry.
他們只要想到我開心自在就會發瘋
Just the concept of me enjoying myself would blow their minds.
你想做什么  從來沒做過的事
What would you like to do? That you've never done?
太多了
So many things.
圣朱尼佩洛是派對之城
San Junipero is a party town.
做什么都行
All up for grabs.
還有兩小時就到午夜了
Midnight's two hours away.
沒多久了
Oh, that's not long.
那為什么要浪費時間坐在這里呢
Why waste time sitting here?
我...
I, um...
-聽著  -沒事的
- Listen... - It's okay.
-不  我是說...  -真的沒事
- No, I mean... - Really, it's okay.
不  我...
No, I'm, uh...
我訂婚了  我有個未婚夫
I'm engaged. I have a fiance.
-他叫格雷格  -格雷格在這里嗎
- He's called Greg. - And is Greg here?
-不  他在...  -其他地方
- No, he's-- - Elsewhere?
對
Yeah.
想跟我上床嗎
Wanna go to bed with me?
我們可以回我家  很快的
We could be back at mine in like...
我從來沒做過那樣的事
I never did anything like that.
那就更應該試試了
All the more reason.
你人很好
Oh, you're nice.
我不行
I can't.
好吧
Okay.
-我只是...我真不能  -我明白
- I just... I can't. - I get it.
-我得走了  -這么大雨
- I have to go. - In this?
認識你真的很高興
It's been really great to meet you.
彼此彼此
Likewise.
好吧
Okay.
該死
Shit.
一周后
搞什么  韋斯
What the hell, Wes?
聽著  我知道我讓你覺得...
Look, I know I'm coming across--
我要對你亮紅燈了  真的
I'm red lighting you, for real.
-好嗎  -不  不要這么做...
- Okay? - No, don't do that. Just...
-那你就別這樣  -你能聽我說完嗎  拜托
- Then stop this. - Can you hear me out? Please? Please.
你覺得圣朱尼佩洛有多少女孩
How many girls do you think there are in San Junipero?
幾百個  幾千個
Hundreds? Thousands?
我不在乎
I don't care.
我是說天涯何處無芳草  韋斯
I'm saying there's plenty of other girls out there for you, Wes.
當地的嗎  她們是死人
The locals? They're like dead people.
這死人也太活躍了吧
A little lively for dead people.
我不想搞什么無聊的浪漫  好嗎
Look, I don't want some kind of boring romance, okay?
像在退休之家似的
Like, Jesus, put us in a retirement home deal.
如果你想找人上床  選擇多的是
Well, if you're looking for someone to fuck, there's options.
-再去泥潭那兒轉轉  -不僅僅是為了性
- Hang out at the Quagmire again. - It's not just sex.
-僅僅是性  -不  我們心有靈犀
- It was just sex. - No, we made a connection.
韋斯  那只是性
Wes, it was just sex.
-不  -沒有情感
- No-- - No roots.
我們玩得很開心
We had fun.
對不起
I'm sorry.
享受這座城市吧
Enjoy the town, for God's sake.
在等人嗎
Waiting for someone?
并沒有
Not really.
我請你喝一杯
I'll get you a drink?
好啊
Uh, yeah, sure.
那...應該是顯微手術吧
So, uh... yeah, it was microsurgery, I guess.
我的兩個膝蓋骨都磨損了
You know, both my kneecaps had kind of just worn down.
我一直不怎么喜歡這首歌  覺得有點奇怪
You know, I never got this song. Kind of weird.
-去跳舞嗎  -好
- Shall we dance? - Sure.
我猜如果當時我把心思放在電腦之類的東西上
I mean, I guess by the time I'd put my mind to, like, computing.
趕上第一股潮流
You know, caught that first wave,
事情就會大不一樣了
would have had a different story.
我要去趟廁所
Gotta use the bathroom.
好吧
Okay.
我不知道該怎么辦
I don't know how to do this.
什么怎么辦
Do what?
幫幫我
Just help me.
你能...
Can you just...
讓我不那么為難嗎
Just make this easy for me?
想上我的車嗎
You wanna get in my car?
-你來這里多久了  -什么
- How long have you been here? - Sorry?
-你來這里多久了  -圣朱尼佩洛嗎
- How long have you been here? - In San Junipero?
幾個月吧
Couple of months.
我打算玩到盡興為止
Plan is long enough to enjoy myself.
我猜我跟你一樣  也是個游客
Guess I'm a tourist, like you.
是啊
Yeah.
你沒事吧
You okay?
沒事
Yeah.
停車
Stop!
抱歉  但是
Sorry, but...
天啊  你的表情
Man, your face!
-喜歡嗎  -太大了
- You like it? - It's just so big.
讓我想起我小時候住的地方
Reminds me of where I grew up.
想你媽媽嗎
Miss your mom?
你得教我
You have to show me.
-好  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
你從來沒和女人上過床嗎
You never slept with a woman before?
我不是在挑剔你
That's not a critique.
剛剛太棒了
I mean, it was fucking awesome.
嗯  從來沒和女人上過床
No, never with a woman.
從來沒和人上過床
Never with anyone.
從來沒有嗎
Not anyone?
-你是說在這城里還是...  -不
- What, in town or...? - No.
哪里都沒有
No one, nowhere.
-看來你給我開苞了  -我給你開苞了
- I guess you deflowered me. - I deflowered you?
什么年代的話  快樂英格蘭嗎
What is this? Merry England?
閉嘴
Shut up.
但是你跟人談過戀愛吧
You've had relationships though.
你可是有未婚夫啊
Hello! You got a fiancé.
-這很復雜  -我猜也是
- It's complicated. - Yeah, I'll say.
你什么時候知道
When did you know...
-你喜歡女人的  -我也喜歡男人
- that you liked women? - I like men too.
權利平等
Equal rights.
好吧
Okay.
但你是什么時候知道的
But when did you know?
你一直都知道嗎
Do you always know?
我曾嫁過一個男人  婚姻維持了挺久
I was married to a guy. A long time, I was married.
我一直知道
I always knew.
我會被其他女孩吸引
I mean, I'd be attracted to other girls,
同事  朋友
co-workers, friends,
為我上菜的服務員
some waitress that served me.
我會迷上她們  瘋狂地迷上
They were crushes. God, they were crushes.
但我從沒采取行動
Never acted on any of it.
從沒做過什么
Never did anything.
我那時愛著他
I was in love with him.
我真的很愛他
I really was in love with him.
但他選擇了離開我
But he chose not to stick around.
現在只有我了
So now it's me.
我不會久留
And I'm passing through.
在我離開之前  我要好好享受
And before I leave, I'll have a good time.
我只想好好享受一番
I'm just gonna have a good time.
時間差不多到了
Time's nearly up.
那我們就躺在這里吧
Then let's lie here.
一周后
打擾
Excuse me?
你見過凱莉嗎
Have you seen Kelly?
-你說什么  -凱莉
- What's that? - Kelly.
我整晚都沒看到她
I haven't seen her all night.
你去泥潭找過了嗎
You tried the Quagmire?
泥潭是什么
What is the Quagmire?
對不起
I'm sorry!
我在哪里見過你
Yeah, I know you from somewhere.
塔克酒吧
Tucker's.
-凱莉的朋友吧  -你知道她在哪里嗎
- Kelly's friend, huh? - Do you know where to find her?
-我怎么會知道  -你是她朋友
- How would I know that? - You're her friend.
-曾經是朋友  -她來過這里嗎
- Was a friend. - Has she been here?
沒有
No.
你也是吧
You too, huh?
試試去別的時間
Try a different time.
80年代  90年代
Here in '80, the '90s,
還有一次是2002年的這里
2002 one time.
她值得你一試  對嗎
She's worth the shot, right?
一周后
接下來為您介紹重新設計的克萊斯勒科爾多瓦
Introducing the totally redesigned Chrysler Cordoba.
1980年  克萊斯勒科爾多瓦
你所期待的奢華應有盡有
All the luxury you expect is here.
但是里程費也不菲...
But so is gas mileage...
不不不
No, no, no.
黃金年代  是吧
Golden age, right?
-是啊  -你要玩還是...
- Right. - You playing or...
對不起  我在找人
I'm sorry, I'm looking for someone.
也許...下次吧
Maybe... next time.
一周后
驚聲尖叫
凱莉
Kelly?
一周后
諜影重重
太好了
Yeah!
干得漂亮
You're beautiful!
選一首歌
Select a song!
去廁所
Ladies' room.
別  你...
No, you--
等等
Wait a minute.
你為什么在這里
Why are you here?
我在找你啊  你去了哪里
I was looking for you. Where did you go?
我想換換音樂聽
I like a change of music.
這怎么會是你的年代
How the hell is this your era?
-你在躲我  -第一  我沒有
- You hid from me. - One, I did not.
第二  我不欠你什么
Two, I owe you zero.
第三  參見第二點
And three... see point two.
這跟誰欠誰無關  這是態度的問題
It's not about who owes who. It's about manners.
你不知道我是誰
You don't know who I am.
你不知道這意味著什么
You don't know what this means.
這意味著樂趣
This means fun.
至少應該是樂趣  而現在...
Or it should. And this...
這可沒什么樂趣  好嗎
This is not fun, okay?
這不是樂趣
This is not fun.
你一點都不難過嗎
So you don't feel bad?
也許你應該感到難過  或者至少有點感覺
Maybe you should feel bad. Or at least feel something.
你們見過一個女孩嗎
Have you seen a girl?
二十多歲  棕發  戴眼鏡
Mid-20s, brown hair, glasses?
天啊
Oh, jeez.
請告訴我你把你的痛感模塊調到零了
Please tell me you got your pain slider set to zero.
嗯  我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
聽著
Okay, listen.
他們有多少人已經死了
How many of them are dead?
第一時間下載無刪減美劇  必須登錄字幕組網站
百分之多少
Like what percentage?
常住居民嗎
As in full-timers?
Eighty. Eighty-five.
更好更快的原創翻譯 雙語字幕
對不起
I'm sorry.
我不會跳的
I'm not gonna jump.
我知道  對不起  不管怎么樣...
I know, and I'm sorry, whatever it's...
我來這兒期間  我說過我不會...
In the time I've been here, I said I wouldn't...
怎么說呢  有感覺
I don't know, do feelings.
你把我嚇壞了
You freaked me out.
我不想喜歡上任何人
I don't want to like anyone.
所以你的出現...真是個大麻煩
So you've been just... totally fucking inconvenient.
那是...
It's that...
我不知道還有多久
I don't know how long there is.
我做不到  我沒為你做好準備
And I can't. I wasn't prepared for you.
想要一些...
For wanting something--
就是下周
Next week it is.
我要結婚了
I'm getting married.
下周
Next week?
嫁給老好人格雷格
To nice Greg?
-你確定要那么做嗎  -我必須那么做
- Sure you're going through with that? - I have to.
你必須
You have to?
他真的是個好人
He really is a good guy.
我的家人并不贊成  但...
I mean, my family don't approve, but...
他們阻止不了我們
they can't stop us.
我知道他可憐我  這讓我很生氣
I know he pities me. That pisses me off.
但這不公平  因為他...
But that's not fair 'cause he's...
你說你不知道還剩多少時間
You said you don't know how much time there is.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
他們告訴我三個月
They tell me three months.
已經幾乎擴散到了全身
It's spread basically everywhere.
他們六個月前就說還有三個月
They said three months before six months ago.
所以他們知道什么呢
So, you know, what do they know?
連點味兒都沒有
Doesn't even taste of anything.
-那你之后會留在這兒嗎  -不
- But so you'll stay here after? - No.
等我結束了  我就到此為止
When I'm done, I am done.
但那太瘋...我是說
But that's cra-- I mean...
-為什么  -理查德
- Why? - Richard.
那是...
That's...
我丈夫叫理查德
My husband's name was Richard.
他兩年前死了
He died just two years ago.
我們本來有機會一起待在圣朱尼佩洛
So we had the opportunity to stay in San Junipero.
他拒絕了
Pass over.
沒抓住機會
Didn't take it.
-他不想  -誰會不想要這個機會
- Didn't want to take it. - Why wouldn't anyone take it?
他有自己的想法
He had his viewpoint.
他有自己相信和不相信的東西
There were things he believed and things he didn't believe in,
他不相信這里
and this place was one of them.
連來這兒看看  體驗一下都不肯
Wouldn't even visit. Take the trial run.
我去
Shit.
我當初也不知道自己是否想來試試  但
I didn't know if I wanted to try it but...
我是說
I mean...
老天  如果沒有這個地方
Jesus, without this place,
我永遠不會認識你這樣的人
I never would've met someone like you.
-怎么不會  -不會的
- Yeah, you could have. - No, I wouldn't.
-我們在外面也可能會認識  -不可能
- We could have met outside all this. - No.
你...
You...
根本不會理解我
would not have got me at all.
不可能
At all.
就算我們真見面了
If we really met, I mean...
真的見面了  你也不會喜歡我
If we really met, you wouldn't like me.
咱們試試
Try me.
或者...你不會想和我待在一起
Or you'd-- You wouldn't want to spend time with me.
-你會來找我  然后  -試試啊
- You'd come and then-- - Try me.
何必呢
Why?
何必呢  有什么意義嗎
Why? What's the point?
怎么  你在哪  休斯敦
What? Where are you? Houston?
內華達州卡森城
Carson City, Nevada.
說吧
So come on.
我都說了我的
I showed you mine.
你在哪
Where are you?
-我可以自己查  -加州圣羅莎
- I can just look it up. - Santa Rosa, California.
-那不遠  -我不希望你...
- That's no distance. - I don't want you to--
我不希望你看到我  我怕...
I don't want you to see me. I'm scared...
我要死了
And I'm dying.
你是什么人都嚇不著我
Whatever you are can't scare me.
讓我去看你吧
Let me come visit.
我想去打個招呼
I want to say hi.
西恩納基金會  療養院
來吧
Here you go.
你還好吧
You okay?
請使用我們提供的磁卡
Please check in at our self-service pods
在自助艙登記
using swipe cards provided.
你就是凱莉吧
You must be Kelly.
應該就是了
I guess I must.
-她在等你  -謝謝
- She's waiting for you. - Thank you.
請
Please.
雖然她身體上無法做出回應
She won't be able to physically respond in any way.
但聽得見
But she can hear you.
不打擾你們了
I'll give you some privacy.
你好啊  小傻瓜
Hello, stupid.
見到你真好
It's good to see you.
你好
Hello.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你是凱莉嗎
Is it... Kelly?
我是
It is.
-我是格雷格  -你就是格雷格
- I'm Greg. - You're Greg?
真見鬼
Holy shit.
你能在她離去之前親自過來見她
Yeah, I think it's great that you came down here in person
這樣真好
before she passes over.
連她家人都不怎么來了  所以
Even her folks don't come visit no more so...
她要去世了嗎
She's passing over?
什么時候
When?
-咱們去喝杯咖啡吧  -好
- Let's go grab a coffee. - Okay.
-她沒告訴你嗎  -沒有
- She didn't tell you? - No, she did not.
說她只是來玩玩
Said she was just visiting.
更確切說  是體驗一下試用版
More like sampling the trial version.
我們才認識三年
I mean, I've only known her the past three years.
靠通信箱交流
We talk on the comm box.
她提過自己怎么會癱瘓嗎
She told you how she ended up quadriplegic?
她那樣有多長時間了
And how long she's been that way?
她21歲時  一天晚上  去父母家
One night, she's 21, comes out to her folks.
他們對那種事有點保守  可以這么說吧
They're a little uptight about it, you might say.
告訴她  他們不想要同性戀女兒
They told her they don't want a gay daughter.
不符合自然規律之類的
It's not natural and so forth.
他們大吵一架
They fight.
她開車駛下了車道
She gets in her car. Runs it off the road.
-21歲時嗎  -四十多年前了
- When she was 21? - More than 40 years back.
可以說她在床上躺了一輩子
It's been her whole lifetime, basically.
所以圣朱尼佩洛系統對她意義重大
So the whole San Junipero system has been a big deal for her.
非常重大
The biggest deal.
當然
Of course now,
等她去世后  就成永久性的了
until she passes over, it goes permanent,
現在她每周限量五小時
she's on a five-hour weekly limit.
大概你也是吧
I guess you're the same.
他們按量來  不肯給多了
They ration it out. They don't trust us with more.
據說給太多你們會瘋的
They say you go crazy if you have too much, you know?
不離開座位  心智與身體分離
You don't leave your seat. You disassociate body from mind.
說得好像有哪家老人院里不是這樣的
Like that doesn't happen in every senior home already.
這系統以治療為目的
The system's there for therapeutic reasons,
沉浸式懷舊療法
immersive nostalgia therapy.
將你投入全是記憶的世界里
Plunge you into a world of memories.
對阿茲海默癥有幫助  他們是這么說的
Helps with Alzheimer's, that's what they say.
小小的幸運
Small mercies.
那么
So...
結婚的事
About this marriage...
本州的安樂死得經過三層確認
The state's got a triple lockdown on euthanasia cases.
你得有醫生  病人
You gotta have a sign-off from the doc,
和一位家庭成員的簽字
the patient, a family member.
防止有的病人
It's to stop folks from passing over
因為太喜歡圣朱尼佩洛而選擇離世
just because they prefer San Junipero flat out.
總之約克夏的家人
Anyhow, Yorkie's family,
他們很虔誠
they're big-time religious,
他們不愿意簽字
and they will not sign.
但配偶的決定有更大的優先級
But a spouse can override them.
-所以你們要結婚  -沒錯
- Hence the wedding bells. - You got it.
我們叫了牧師明天上午來
We got a pastor coming tomorrow a.m.,
她已安排好明天下午就離世
and then she's scheduled to pass tomorrow afternoon.
"安排好離世"  就直說死吧
"Scheduled to pass." Let's just call it dying.
如果你可以這么說的話
If you can call it dying.
上傳到云端  聽著像天堂似的
Uploaded to the cloud, sounds like heaven.
也許吧
I guess.
你會穿西裝嗎
You gonna wear a suit?
婚禮是在我休息時舉行
The ceremony's on my coffee break.
我沒結過  所以就想著
I never married so I just figured,
會有什么損害呢
you know, what's the harm?
你是個好人
You're a good man.
舉手之勞  對吧
It's the least I could do, right?
你現在能幫我們接入系統嗎
Think you could hook us up to the system now?
就一會兒  在她離世之前
Just for a little while, before she passes?
你之后還是能見到她的
You can still see her afterwards.
到時她就不受限了
I mean, then she's no limit.
她將成為圣朱尼佩洛的永久居民
She's full, fat, permanent San Juniperan.
我知道  但拜托你了
I know, but can you?
說真的  這里很嚴格  他們隨時監控
Seriously, it is so tight here that they monitor every--
我就只要一會兒
I only want a moment.
女士
Ma'am.
-五分鐘  -謝謝
- You got five minutes - Thank you.
我還從沒白天來過
I've never been here during the daylight.
很暖和
It's warm.
我長話短說  我跟格雷格聊過了
Listen, I gotta be quick. So I spoke to Greg.
-你明天就要離世了  -是的
- You're passing over tomorrow? - Yeah.
婚禮幾小時后
Couple of hours after the wedding.
嚴格上說  我要永遠在這兒度蜜月了
So I guess I am technically honeymooning here forever.
對不起我沒告訴你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
-我要說點瘋狂的話  -好吧
- I'm gonna say something crazy. - Okay.
你愿和我結婚嗎
Wanna marry me instead?
格雷格看起來人不錯  但是
It's just... Greg seems great, but...
為什么不和與你心靈相通的人結婚呢
Why not someone you've connected with?
這是答應了嗎
Is that a yes?
成為你的合法妻子
...to be your lawfully wedded wife,
相互擁有  相互扶持
to have and to hold,
無論疾病還是健康
in sickness and in health,
無論順境還是逆境
in good times and in woe,
富裕還是貧窮
for richer, for poorer...
所有系統暫停
抓穩
Hold tight.
好了
There you go.
快到了
Nearly there.
好的
That's it.
你確定自己沒事嗎
Are you sure you're all right?
你都不為我打扮好嗎
You didn't dress up to see me?
拜托
Come on!
這樣呢
Better?
看起來好真實
Looks so real.
感覺好真實
It feels so real!
-你在干什么  -我愛這里
- What are you doing? - Oh, I love it here!
好愛這里
I just love it.
-你以前也來過啊  -但現在我住在這里了
- You've been here before. - But now I live here!
和我待在一起吧
Be with me.
-我們現在就在一起  -我不是這個意思
- I'm with you now. - That's not what I mean.
離世
Pass over.
-你什么時候到日子  -約克夏
- When it's your time. - Yorkie.
-和我留在這里  -我們就不能享受今晚嗎
- Stay here with me. - Can we just enjoy tonight?
快到午夜了
It's almost midnight.
十分鐘后  你就離開這里了
In ten minutes, you're out of here.
我要等一周才能再次見到你
Then I gotta wait a week to see you again.
你知道我只是個游客
You know I'm just a visitor.
再過幾個月  然后呢
What, a couple of months, then what?
-我們現在不討論這個  -然后你就死了
- We're not discussing this. - Then you're gone.
就離開了
Just gone.
-你可以擁有永恒的  -永恒
- You could have forever. - Forever?
永恒是什么意思啊
Who can even make sense of forever?
你想多久就多久
However long you want then.
你也可以輕易抹除自己
I mean, you can remove yourself like that.
這里不是個籠子
It's not a trap.
看看這一切
I mean, look at it!
老天  摸摸這個
Jesus! Touch it!
我要走了
I'm going.
這是真的
It's real.
這些都是真的
This is real.
還有這個
And this.
拜托  你知道這只是個動作
Come on. You know that was just a gesture.
-你娶了我  -為了幫你離世
- You married me. - To help you pass over.
-是出于好意  -離開就不那么好了
- As a... kindness. - It's not so kind to leave.
好吧  聽著  對不起  我只是
Okay, look, look, I'm sorry, I just...
我有這個機會
I got this chance.
我們有這個機會  我想和你分享
We got this chance. I wanna share it with you.
我說了我已經決定了
I said I made my choice.
為什么  因為你丈夫不在這里所以你很愧疚
What is it? You feel bad because your husband isn't here?
-因為那是他的選擇  -不要這樣
- Because that was his choice. - Don't.
他選擇不留在這里  就像他離開了你
He chose not to stay here. It's like he left you.
他本來可以留下  但他選擇離開你
You know, he could have stayed, but he chose to leave you.
你根本不知道自己在說什么
You don't know what you're saying.
你應該感覺生氣
You should be mad at him.
-而不是用愧疚懲罰自己  -放手
- Not whipping yourself with guilt. - Get off me.
你不明白  但他做的事實際上很自私
You can't see it! But what he did, it was selfish actually!
49年
Forty-nine years...
我和他在一起49年
I was with him for 49 years.
你根本無從想象
You can't begin to imagine.
你根本不懂
You can't know...
我們的羈絆  承諾  厭倦
the bond, the commitment, the boredom,
渴望  歡樂  以及愛情
the yearning, the laughter, the love of it.
該死的愛情  你根本不懂
The fucking love. You just cannot know!
我們犧牲的一切
Everything we sacrificed.
我給予他的那些歲月  他給予我的那些歲月
The years I gave him. The years he gave me.
你想過問我嗎
Did you think to ask?
你有想過問我嗎
Did it occur to you to ask?
我們有個女兒
We had a daughter.
艾莉森
Alison.
一直很難搞  一直很美好
Always difficult, always beautiful.
39歲時死了  上帝保佑她
Died at 39 years old, bless her heart.
理查德和我  我們都心如刀割
And Richard and I, we felt that heartbreak as one.
你以為只有自己飽嘗痛苦嗎  去你媽的
You think you're the only person ever suffered, go fuck yourself.
-我不知道  -你也沒想知道
- Well, I didn't know-- - Didn't think to.
理查德要死的時候  他說
You know, when he was dying, richard said to me
他們給他提供這個機會  離世  來這里
when they offered him this, to pass over, pass through,
在這個你熱愛的墓地里永生
spend eternity in this fucking graveyard you're so in love with,
他說  "我怎么能
he said, "How can I?
她錯過了機會  我怎么能"
When she missed out, how can I?"
所以他直接走了
And so he went.
我希望自己能相信他現在和女兒在一起
And I wish I could believe he's with her now,
父女團聚  但我做不到
that they're together, but I don't.
我認為他們哪都不在  就像你說的
I believe they're nowhere. Just like you said.
沒了  不  我是可憐你
Gone. No, I pitied you,
這就是真相  我可憐你
and that's the truth. I pitied you.
現在你想向我推銷
Now you give me some sales pitch
這種永恒有多他媽美好
about how fucking peachy forever could be.
對不起
I'm sorry.
你想在沒有意義的地方永生嗎
You wanna spend forever somewhere nothing matters?
最后像韋斯那樣
End up like Wes?
像那些在泥潭放縱的傻逼
All those lost fucks at the Quagmire
拼盡全力想要感受到什么  那就去吧
trying anything to feel something, go ahead.
但我要退出了  我走了
But I'm out. I'm gone.
凱莉  對不起
Kelly, I'm sorry.
凱莉
Kelly!
前方封路
凱莉
Hey, Kelly.
-你還好嗎  -我沒事
- You all right? - Yeah, I am fine.
那好吧
Well, okay then.
凱莉
Kelly?
總得說來
All things considered...
我想我準備好了
I guess I'm ready.
準備好什么
For what?
面對剩下的一切
For the rest of it.
艾莉森·西西莉亞·布斯  享年39歲
理查德·艾倫·布斯  享年74歲
凱莉·簡·布斯  享年73歲
長眠于此
準備好了嗎
Ready?
圣朱尼佩洛